<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cockatrice_carddatabase version="4">
    <sets>
        <set>
            <name>NR</name>
            <longname>Northern Realms</longname>
            <settype>Custom</settype>
            <releasedate>2020-05-21</releasedate>
        </set>
        <set>
            <name>NG</name>
            <longname>Nilfgaard</longname>
            <settype>Custom</settype>
            <releasedate>2020-05-21</releasedate>
        </set>
        <set>
            <name>GW</name>
            <longname>Gwent Neutral Cards</longname>
            <settype>Custom</settype>
            <releasedate>2020-05-21</releasedate>
        </set>
        <set>
            <name>MO</name>
            <longname>Monsters</longname>
            <settype>Custom</settype>
            <releasedate>2020-05-21</releasedate>
        </set>
        <set>
            <name>ST</name>
            <longname>ScoiaTael</longname>
            <settype>Custom</settype>
            <releasedate>2020-05-21</releasedate>
        </set>
        <set>
            <name>SK</name>
            <longname>Skellige</longname>
            <settype>Custom</settype>
            <releasedate>2020-05-21</releasedate>
        </set>
    </sets>
    <cards>

<!-- [NR] NORTHERN REALMS -->
        <card>
            <name>King Foltest</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Stubborn, Loyal, Leader, Legendary.

Spawn: Foltest. Deploy: Boost all Loyal Bronze and Silver Units in your Hand and Deck by 1.
Note: Won't Boost Disloyal Units anymore</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/CcoawFI.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>King Henselt</name>
            <text>2 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Stubborn, Leader, Loyal, Legendary.

Spawn Henselt. Deploy: Choose a Bronze Ally. Play all copies of it from your Deck.
General change: Promote effects were mostly removed (except for Impera Enforcers until (...)) and forged into Armor.
General change: Added Doomed and Stubborn Tags to all Leaders due to their new ability of Spawning themselves.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/8nU85dH.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>King Radovid V</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Stubborn, Leader, Loyal, Legendary.

Spawn: Radovid. Deploy: Toggle 2 Units' Lock. If Enemies, Damage them by 4 as well.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/HkQEKMX.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Bloody Baron</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Gold, Loyal, Legendary.

If this Unit is in your Deck at the end of the Round, place it on top. Whenever an Enemy is Destroyed during a Round while this Unit is in your Deck, Boost it by 1.
Bug Fix:  Fixed an issue with Bloody Baron being Boosted by Units moved to the Graveyard at the end of the round. Bloody Baron will now be Boosted even when yours and your enemy's Units are destroyed at the same time. Fixed an issue whereby Bloody Baron would be moved to the top of the deck at the start of the round, instead of at the end of round.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/hYbFaCv.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dandelion</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Gold, Loyal, Legendary.

Deploy: Boost up to 3 Bronze or Silver Units in your Deck by 3. Shuffle the others back.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/QOQAj8W.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>John Natalis</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Gold, Loyal, Legendary.

Deploy: Force all Northern Realms Machine Allies to Damage a random Enemy by 2.
John Natalis will no longer Weaken self for each Unit affected.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/pHx9Mbi.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Keira Metz</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Mage, Gold, Loyal, Legendary.

Deploy: Spawn Quen Sign, Epidemic or Thunderbolt Potion.
Now Loyal-only.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/kKomPy4.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Philippa Eilhart</name>
            <text>1 Strength, Agile, Mage, Gold, Loyal, Legendary.

Deploy: Damage an Enemy by 5, then Damage random Enemies by 4, 3, 2 and 1. The same Enemy cannot be Damaged twice in a row.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/VYdsNH1.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Priscilla</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, 4-Turn Timer, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Every turn, at the end of your turn, Boost a random Ally (but never self) by 3. Ability discontinues after the Unit Boosts Allies 4 times without leaving the Board.
Note: Will shuffle itself into the Deck instead of being put on the bottom.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/ILNDnXT.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Shani</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Resurrect a Unit and add 4 Armor to it.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/PxPMmnE.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Sigismund Dijkstra</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Agile, Gold, Disloyal, Legendary.

Deploy: Play the top 2 cards in your Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/okBTz9Z.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Triss: Butterfly Spell</name>
            <text>Neutral, 5 Strength, Agile, Mage, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Every turn, at the start of your turn, Boost all other Lowest Allies by 1.== </text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/Lkc7TFj.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Vernon Roche</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Blue Stripes, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Damage an Enemy by 3. If it was Destroyed, Spawn a Blue Stripes Commando on a random row and repeat the Deploy ability (one time only).</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/mPVWaUb.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Botchling</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Melee, Cursed, Silver, Loyal, Epic.

Deploy: Boost all Lubberkins in your Hand, Deck and Graveyard by 5. Deathwish: Play a Lubberkin from your Deck.
No longer a Token, became a standalone NR Card. Added Cursed Tag. Removed Fleeting Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/r8RAYBe.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dethmold</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Siege, Mage, Silver, Loyal, Epic.

Deploy: Spawn Torrential Rain, Clear Skies or Alzur's Thunder.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/0JD1Bjd.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Lubberkin</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Ranged, Cursed, Silver, Loyal, Epic.

Deploy: Boost all Botchlings in your Hand, Deck and Graveyard by 5. Deathwish: Play a Botchling from your Deck.
No longer a Token, became a standalone NR Card. Removed Fleeting Tag. Added Cursed Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/6a0Ujt4.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Margarita of Aretuza</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Siege, Mage, Silver, Loyal, Epic.

Deploy: Reset a Unit and toggle its Lock.
Aretuza Adept is no longer a Token, became a standalone NR card. ex-Ban Ard Adept has returned to the game as Nilfgaard's Vicovaro Novice standalone card.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/dzrTYdX.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Nenneke</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Siege, Silver, Loyal, Epic.

Deploy: Shuffle up to 3 cards from your Graveyard into your Deck.
Bug Fix: Fixed improper descriptions of Assire var Anahid's and Nenneke's carousels</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/BxM20CU.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Odrin</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Silver, Loyal, Epic.

Every turn, at the start of your turn, move this Unit to a random row and Boost all Units on it by 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/Wbaoxk2.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Prince Stennis</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Agile, Silver, Loyal, Epic.

Every 2 turns, at the start of your turn, Boost this Unit by the number of Machine Allies. Crewmen 1. Deploy: Gain 2 Armor.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/v3FpJmm.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Princess Pavetta</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Ranged, Doomed, Mage, Silver, Loyal, Epic.

Deploy: If neither player has passed, shuffle the Lowest Ally into your Deck, then shuffle the Lowest Enemy into your opponent's Deck. Does not affect Pavetta.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/yOJFUv6.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Reinforcements</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Silver, Epic.

Play a Bronze or Silver Unit from your Deck. Shuffle the others back.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/M7Waa4K.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Sabrina Glevissig</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Agile, Mage, Silver, Disloyal, Epic.

Deathwish: Set all Units on the row to the Power of the Lowest Unit on the row.
Bug Fix: Fixed an issue with Sabrina Glevissig changing Units' Power to 0 if destroyed in a chain with another Unit on her row.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/9dR3SXB.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Síle de Tansarville</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Ranged, Mage, Silver, Loyal, Epic.

Deploy: You may play a Bronze Special card from your Hand. If you do, draw the top card from your Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/mJ1X7oU.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Thaler</name>
            <text>11 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Silver, Disloyal, Epic.

Deploy: Draw the top 2 cards from your Deck. Keep 1 and shuffle the other back.
Thaler's ability is no longer optional.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/LwUFuxf.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Trollololo</name>
            <text>Trollololo, 8 Strength, Agile, Ogroid, Silver, Loyal, Epic.

Counts as part of any Northern Realms Trio on the row. Deploy: Gain 5 Armor.
Added Ogroid Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/h4ZAgfH.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ves</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Melee, Blue Stripes, Silver, Loyal, Epic.

Whenever you complete a Northern Realms Trio, play this Unit from your Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/5mMsGnx.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Aretuza Adept</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Siege, Mage, Bronze, Loyal, Rare.

Deploy: Play a random Bronze Weather card from your Deck.
No longer a Token, became a standalone NR card. Removed Fleeting Tag. Added Mage Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/Vow5TxQ.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ballista</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Siege, Machine, Bronze, Loyal, Common.

Deploy: Damage an Enemy and up to 3 other random Enemies with the same Power by 1. Fresh Crew: Repeat the Deploy ability.
No longer ignores Armor.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/upzOzF6.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Blue Stripe Commando</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Agile, Blue Stripes, Bronze, Loyal, Rare.

Whenever a different Ally with the same Power as this Unit is played, play this Unit from your Deck (1 copy max) and place it on that Ally's row. Whenever you complete a Blue Stripes Commando Trio, create 1 base copy of a Blue Stripes Commando on the bottom of your Deck.
Bug Fix: Changed Blue Stripes Commandos' priorities so they summon properly when Kaedweni Siege Support is present.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/nuSS2IU.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Blue Stripe Scout</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Blue Stripes, Bronze, Loyal, Common.

Deploy: Gain 2 Armor. Deploy: Clear weather from the row on your side Crewmen: 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/eB601Qc.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dun Banner</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Ranged, Bronze, Loyal, Rare.

If at the start of your turn you have not passed and are losing the Round by more than 20 Power, play this Unit from your Deck
Reworked Weather. Removed Weather Immunity.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/s8wTdKF.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Field Medic</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Siege, Bronze, Loyal, Common.

Deploy: Choose a different Bronze Ally and shuffle it back into your Deck, then play a random Bronze Unit from your Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/XCVIDye.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Kaedweni Cavalry</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Siege, Bronze, Loyal, Rare.

Deploy: Remove Armor from 2 Units and Boost self by the amount of Armor removed.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/OXZTrPq.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Kaedweni Sergeant</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Agile, Bronze, Loyal, Common.

Deploy: Boost by 1 this Unit and all Bronze Loyal Units with the same Power in your Hand, Deck or on your side of the Board. Crewmen 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/ovCWg7x.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Poor Fucking Infantry</name>
            <text>Temporarily removed from the game.

</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/stptSr1.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Reaver Hunter</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Bronze, Loyal, Common.

Deploy or Bond: Boost all Reaver Hunters in your Hand, Deck and on your side of the Board by 1. When a Revear Hunter Trio is completed, Damage the Highest Enemy by half its Power (rounding down and ignoring Armor).
Note: Reaver Hunter will no longer buff copies in the Graveyard.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/ijxjjsC.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Reaver Scout</name>
            <text>1 Strength, Ranged, Bronze, Loyal, Rare.

Deploy: Choose a different Bronze Ally. Play a copy of it from your Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/LFp81hA.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Redanian Elite</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Bronze, Loyal, Rare.

Whenever this Unit's Armor reaches 0, Boost self by 5. Deploy: Gain 4 Armor.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/KYnpolx.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Redanian Knight</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Bronze, Loyal, Common.

Every turn, at the start of your turn, if this Unit has no Armor, Boost it by 2 and add 2 Armor to it.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/8kg6vHt.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Redanian Knight-Elect</name>
            <text>Redanian Knight-Elect, 5 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

If this Unit has Armor at the start of your turn, Boost Units adjacent to it by 1. Deploy: Gain 2 Armor.
Note: Promote was removed from the game and transformed into Redanian Knight-Elect unit. Promotion was removed and forged into Armor.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/WCL53fs.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Reinforced Ballista</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Machine, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Damage an Enemy by 2. Fresh Crew: Repeat the Deploy ability.
Note: Reinforced Ballista will not ignore Armor when damaging now.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/bCmcCmN.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Reinforced Trebuchet</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Siege, Machine, 1-Turn Timer, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Every turn, at the start of your turn, Damage a random Enemy by 1.
Note: Won't ignore Armor anymore.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/CfLJN1G.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Siege Master</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Agile, Bronze, Loyal, Common.

Deploy: Return a Machine Ally to your Hand and immediately play it again. Crewmen 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/595IXyF.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Siege Support</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Bronze, Loyal, Rare.

Whenever an Ally appears, Boost it by 1. If it's a Machine, Boost it by 1 and add 1 Armor. Crewmen 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/6Pk4iBx.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Siege Tower</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Machine, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Add 2 Armor to Units adjacent to this Unit. Fresh Crew: Boost self by 3.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/F8frnoK.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Temerian Infantry</name>
            <text>Temerian Infantryman, 3 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Play all Temerian Infantrymen from your Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/xXsP5Lm.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Tridam Infantry</name>
            <text>Tridam Infantryman, 8 Strength, Melee, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Gain 3 Armor. .</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/14AfXCv.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Trebuchet</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Agile, Machine, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Damage 3 Adjacent Units by 1. Fresh Crew: Increase the Damage dealt by 1.
Note: Trebuchet will not ignore Armor when damaging now.
Bug Fix: Fixed an issue with Trebuchet not shooting when deployed next to Locked Units with Crewmen.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/EllWmqE.jpg">NR</set>
        </card>

<!-- [GW] Neutral -->


        <card>
            <name>Avallac'h</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Elf, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: If neither player has passed, both players draw the top 2 cards from their Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/OXAnzSU.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Chironex</name>
            <text>1 Strength, Siege, Doomed, Beast, Loyal, Silver, Yennefer Token.

Deploy: Damage all other Units by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/hiJwGDJ.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ciri</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

At the end of the Round, return this Unit to your Hand if you lost.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/IKFnAuV.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ciri: Dash</name>
            <text>9 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

When this Unit enters the Graveyard, Strengthen it by 3 and shuffle it back into your Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/T9VsyBv.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dudu</name>
            <text>1 Strength, Agile, Relict, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Choose an Enemy and copy its Power.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/BidfkqQ.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Eskel</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Melee, Witcher, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Play Vesemir and Lambert from your deck. Note: Potions will no longer give additional buffs to Witchers.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/7EbVM1Z.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Francis Bedlam</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Ranged, Regressing, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy, Brave: Strengthen self enough to tie the Round or to a maximum of 15 base Power.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/fZdWUsi.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Gaunter O'Dimm</name>
            <text>Neutral, 5 Strength, Agile, Relict, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Guess whether a random Bronze or Silver Unit from your opponent’s Deck is Higher or Lower than 5. Success: Play any card from your Deck. Shuffle the others back. Failure: Your opponent draws the top Bronze or Silver card from their Deck. Tie: Both players draw the top Bronze or Silver card from their Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/D5pM0j7.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Geralt of Rivia</name>
            <text>10 Strength, Agile, Witcher, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy, Brave: Strengthen self by 3.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/4BUJoG1.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Geralt: Aard</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Witcher, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Push 5 adjacent Enemies on the row above them and Damage them by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/OnTLMEI.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Geralt: Igni</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Witcher, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Destroy the strongest non-Gold unit(s) on the opposite row if that row totals 20 or more strength.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/1Bab0L1.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Iris von Everec</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Agile, Disloyal, Silver, Epic.

Deathwish: Boost all Units on the other side of the Board by 3.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/44ELpWJ.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Johnny</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Siege, Relict, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Discard a card in your Hand (can be Gold), then create a copy in your Hand of a card of the same color in your opponent’s Deck. 
Note: Johnny will not discard the card if the opponent's deck lacks a card of the relevant color.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/ihU7EzC.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Korathi Heatwave</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Weather, Gold, Legendary.

Apply Drought on all Rows on your opponent's side. Drought: Every Turn, at the start of your Turn, Damage one of the Lowest Units on the row by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/BtdUsmP.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Lambert</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Melee, Witcher, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Play Vesemir and Eskel from your deck. Note: Potions will no longer give additional buffs to Witchers.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/Iz7db9K.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Manticore Venom</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Silver, Epic.

Damage 5 adjacent Units by 4.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/Em8bBhu.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Marching Orders</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Silver, Epic.

Boost 1 of the Lowest Bronze or Silver Units in your Deck by 2 and play it.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/IU9YZNF.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Merigold's Hailstorm</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Silver, Epic. Note: Removed Weather and Fleeting tags.

Damage all Units on a row by half their Power (rounding down and ignoring Armor). Added new, unique VFX to Merigold's Hailstorm.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/6vWBcX1.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Myrgtabrakke</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Ranged, Draconid, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Damage Units by 2, 2 and then 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/S6Qin73.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Necromancy</name>
            <text>Necromancy, Neutral, Event, Special, Silver, Epic.

Banish a Unit from either Graveyard and Boost an Ally by its Power.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/D4VZdFq.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ocvist</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Siege, Draconid, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

After 4 turns, at the start of your turn, Damage all Enemies by 1, return this Unit to your Hand and Transform it into Exhausted Ocvist.
Exhausted Ocvist: 6 Strength, Siege, Draconid, Loyal, Silver. No ability.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/OukYGjN.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Olgierd von Everec</name>
            <text>9 Strength, Melee, Cursed, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

When this Unit is Discarded or Destroyed, Weaken it by half (rounding up). At the start of Rounds 2 and 3, Resurrect this Unit, if it is in the Graveyard. Note: Olgierd's power will now be reduced upon death rather than resurrection.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/eEi4c6Y.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Operator</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Ranged, Mage, Doomed, Stubborn, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Choose a Bronze Unit in your Hand and create a base copy of it in both players' Hands.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/h6Sxqyn.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Prize-Winning Cow</name>
            <text>2 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Beast, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Retaliation: Spawn a Chort on the row. Deathwish: Spawn a Chort on the row.
Chort: 6 Strength, Agile, Relict, Loyal, Bronze. Deploy, Brave: Strengthen self by 4.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/btVuFbj.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ragh Nar Roog</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Weather, Gold, Legendary.

Apply Ragh Nar Roog to all rows on your opponent’s side. Ragh Nar Roog: Every turn, at the start of your turn, damage 1 of the Highest Units on the row by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/S65zYfb.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Regis</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Vampire, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Timer 2, Turn Start, Boost self by 7, if you are winning the Round. Note: Removed Higher Vampire token. Note: Removed Relentless tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/9Su73X2.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Regis: Higher Vampire</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Vampire, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Look at 3 random Bronze Units from your opponent's Deck. Consume 1, Boost self by base Power of consumed Unit, then shuffle the others back.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/JIEEW6Z.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Renew</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Gold, Legendary.

Resurrect a Gold Unit from your Graveyard.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/9hcmtMe.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Roach</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Beast, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Whenever you play a Gold Unit from your Hand, play Roach from your Deck on a random row before that Unit's Deploy ability resolves.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/jG2lcgy.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Royal Decree</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Gold, Legendary.

Play a Gold card from your Deck. Shuffle the others back..</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/Nnd7r2G.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Sarah</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Siege, Relict, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Shuffle a card from your Hand (can be Gold) back into your Deck, then draw the top different card of the same color from your Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/IXpJZfk.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Scorch</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Silver, Epic.

Destroy all the Highest Units.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/nBlIh7R.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Skellige Storm</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Weather, Silver, Epic.

Apply Skellige Storm to a row on your opponent’s side. Skelige Storm: Every turn, at the start of your turn, Damage the leftmost units on the row by 2, 2 and 1, respectively.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/fZnUVmg.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Summoning Circle</name>
            <text>Summoning Circle, Neutral, Special, Event, Silver, Epic.

Spawn a base copy of the last Enemy your opponent played from their Hand. Note: Lesser Golem became a standalone unit.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/dIpfJnc.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>The Last Wish</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Silver, Epic.

Draw your top 2 Bronze or Silver cards. Play 1 and shuffle the other back.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/kkDUqEX.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Triss Merigold</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Agile, Mage, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Damage a Unit by 5.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/ebsfBHj.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Triss: Butterflies</name>
            <text>Neutral, 5 Strength, Agile, Mage, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Every turn, at the start of your turn, Boost all other Lowest Allies by 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/cSEWIVf.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Unicorn</name>
            <text>1 Strength, Siege, Doomed, Beast, Loyal, Silver, Yennefer Token.

Deploy: Boost all other Units by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/hXWPEoI.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Vaedermakar</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Silver, Epic.

Play a Weather card from your Deck. Shuffle the others back (couldn't find the official text).</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/HXnFbIl.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Vesemir</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Melee, Witcher, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Play Eskel and Lambert from your Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/re8oipO.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Villentretenmerth</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Draconid, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

After 3 turns, at the start of your turn, Destroy all the Highest Units on the Board.
Note: Will only Destroy the Highest Unit(s) once.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/XkXlLwb.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>White Frost</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Weather, Silver, Epic.

Apply Frost to a row on your opponent’s side and the row above it. Frost: Every turn, at the start of your turn, Damage one of the Lowest Units on the row by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/eHObWir.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Yennefer of Vengerberg</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Mage, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Spawn a Unicorn or a Chironex.
Unicorn: 1 Strength, Siege, Doomed, Beast, Loyal, Silver. Deploy: Boost all other Units by 2.
Chironex: 1 Strength, Siege, Doomed, Beast, Loyal, Silver. Deploy: Damage all other Units by 2.
Note: Replaced Fleeting with Doomed Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/m4VTp9R.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Yennefer: Conjurer</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Mage, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Turn Start: Damage the Highest Enemy/Enemies by 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/ZEJjZZq.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Zoltan: Scoundrel</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Agile, Dwarf, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Spawn Field Marshal Duda Companion or Field Marshal Duda Agitator.
Field Marshal Duda: Agitator; 1 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Beast, Disloyal, Silver. Deploy: Damage 2 adjacent Units on either side by 2.
Field Marshal Duda: Companion; 1 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Beast, Loyal, Silver. Deploy: Boost 2 adjacent Units on either side by 2.
Note: Replaced Fleeting with Doomed Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/LQYeEaT.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Alzur's Double–Cross</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Silver, Epic.

Boost one of the Highest Bronze or Silver Units in your Deck by 2, and play it.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/cE6tn0n.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Bekker's Dark Mirror</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Silver, Epic.

Swap the Power of the Highest and Lowest Unit on the Board. Note: Doesn't affect gold cards anymore.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/phTCnra.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Carlo Varese</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Melee, Dwarf, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Toggle a Unit’s Lock.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/fZnUVmg.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Commander's Horn</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Silver, Epic.

Boost 5 adjacent units by 4.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/IqT8ZWr.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Cyprian Wiley</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Siege, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Weaken a Unit by 3 or Destroy an Ambush Unit.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/fZ1nUUT.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Decoy</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Silver, Epic.

Return an Ally to your Hand, Boost it by 3 and play it.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/LjQwRxF.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Adrenaline Rush</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Bronze, Rare.

Toggle a Unit’s Resilience.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/3mLrVDA.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Alzur's Thunder</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Bronze, Common.

Remove 7 strength from a non-Gold unit.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/LySG6pc.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Arachas Venom</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Bronze, Common.

Damage 3 adjacent Units by 4. .</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/FiO6EAA.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Biting Frost</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Weather, Bronze, Common.

Apply Frost to a row on your opponent’s side. Frost: Every turn, at the start of your turn, Damage the Lowest Unit on the row by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/4xTGa22.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Clear Skies</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Bronze, Common.

Spawn Clear Skies or Rally.
Clear Skies: Event, Doomed, Bronze. Trigger all Weather on your side, then clear all Weather from your side.
Rally: Event, Doomed, Bronze. Play a random Bronze Unit from your Deck.
Clarified Clear Skies' tooltip due to Weather rework. Removed Fleeting tag from First Light. Removed Weather tag from Clear Skies. Removed Special tag from Clear Skies and Rally. Added Doomed tag to Clear Skies and Rally.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/VbkZYpN.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dimeritium Bomb</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Silver, Epic.

Choose 3 adjacent units. Reset them to base strength. Convert affected Gold units to Silver or Bronze (their original color). (couldn't find the official text).</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/vP5NaeD.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dimeritium Shackles</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Bronze, Rare.

Lock or Unlock any unit on the battlefield. If Gold, convert it to Silver (or Bronze, if that was its original color). Locked units lose all tokens and have no ability until replayed or moved to a hand.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/rksdOrC.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Elder Bear</name>
            <text>10 Strength, Melee, Cursed, Beast, Loyal, Bronze, Raging Berserker Token. 

No Ability. Note: Removed Bear and Shapeshifter tags. Added Beast and Cursed tags. Note: Weather Immunity was removed.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/kD1NEIt.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Epidemic</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Bronze, Rare, [http://imgur.com/a/M0A1d Illustration].

Destroy the weakest non-Gold unit(s) on the battlefield.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/m6OiFSu.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Impenetrable Fog</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Weather, Bronze, Common.

Apply Fog to a row on your opponent's side. Fog: Every turn, at the start of your turn, Damage the Highest Unit on the row by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/ob7me8J.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Lacerate</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Bronze, Rare.

Damage all units on a row by 3.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/dRmdefh.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Petri's Philter</name>
            <text>Event, Bronze, Special, Rare.

Boost 3 adjacent Units by 3 and add 3 Armor to them.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/RYRvrQb.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Stammelford's Tremors</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Bronze, Rare.

Damage up to 6 random Enemies by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/4DCXdMd.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Swallow</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Bronze, Common.

Boost a Unit by 8. Note: Removed Potion tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/epfYp4j.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Thunderbolt</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Bronze, Common.

Boost 3 adjacent units by 4. Note: Removed Potion Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/1m4jv6B.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Torrential Rain</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Weather, Bronze, Common.

Apply Rain to a row on your opponent’s side. Rain: Every turn, at the start of your turn, Damage up to 5 of the Lowest Units on the row by 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/i3qszbh.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Bloodcurdling Roar</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Bronze, Rare.

Destroy an Ally. Spawn a Bear.
Bear: 11 Strength, Agile, Beast, Doomed, Loyal, Bronze. No Ability.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/gZxgA8a.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Mardroeme</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Bronze, Rare.

Reset a Unit and Strengthen it by 3; or Reset a Unit and Weaken it by 3.
Mutagen: Event, Doomed, Bronze. Reset a Unit and Strengthen it by 3.
Spores: Event, Doomed, Bronze. Reset a Unit and Weaken it by 3.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/RfusXCK.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Quen Sign</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Bronze, Common.

Choose a Unit in your Hand. Give all copies of it in your Hand and Deck a Shield and Boost them by 2. Units which already have Shield cannot be chosen and aren't affected.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/IYtS06l.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Shrike</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Bronze, Rare.

Boost up to 6 random Allies by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/craGp9P.jpg">GW</set>
        </card>

<!-- [MO] Monsters -->


        <card>
            <name>Dagon</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Stubborn, Loyal, Leader, Legendary.

Spawn: Dagon. Deploy: Spawn Biting Frost, Impenetrable Fog or Torrential Rain.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/BPTp9fW.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Eredin Bréacc Glas</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Stubborn, Wild Hunt, Loyal, Leader, Legendary.

Spawn: Eredin. Deploy: Spawn a Bronze Wild Hunt Unit. Note: Removed Weather Immunity. Note: Removed Eredin token.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/UUsfhuk.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Unseen Elder</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Stubborn, Vampire, Loyal, Leader, Legendary.

Spawn: Unseen Elder. Deploy: Deploy: Consume 3 Allies, but Strengthen this unit by their power instead of Boosting.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/Vv6kjq5.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Woodland Spirit</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Relict, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Spawn 3 Rabid Wolves and apply Fog to the opposite row. Note: Removed Weather Immunity.
Rabid Wolf: 1 Strength, Melee, Beast, Loyal, Bronze.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/ZXAEXpa.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Caranthir Ar-Feiniel</name>
            <text>9 Strength, Agile, Wild Hunt, Mage, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Move 3 Enemies to this Unit's row on your opponent's side and apply Frost to that row on that side only.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/jY0Mmex.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Caretaker</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Relict, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Resurrect a unit from your opponent’s Graveyard.
Added Relict tag. Can no longer resurrect Permadeath units, known as Doomed now.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/mojhRH4.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Draug</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Agile, Specter, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Damage a random Enemy by 1 (ignoring Armor). Repeat 6 times.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/y1Tj8QB.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ge'els</name>
            <text>2 Strength, Agile, Wild Hunt, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Draw the top Gold card and top Silver card from your Deck. Play one and return the other to the top of your Deck. Note: No longer a Leader.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/cDeEjJL.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Imlerith</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Wild Hunt, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Damage an Enemy by 4. If the Enemy is under Frost, Damage it by 8 instead.
Reworked Weather, removed Weather Immunity.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/gkhtWAN.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Katakan</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Melee, Vampire, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Consume a Unit from either Graveyard.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/nHxl9J6.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Kayran</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Insectoid, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Consume a Unit from your Hand, then Boost self by an additional 8.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/i7VDTOq.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Miruna</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Beast, Loyal / Disloyal, Gold, Legendary.

If played on your opponent’s side, then after 2 turns, at the end of your turn, move the Highest other Unit on its row to your side.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/jkshiug.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Old Speartip</name>
            <text>10 Strength, Agile, Ogroid, Loyal, Gold. 

If at the start of your turn there are 2 or fewer Units on the opposite row, fall asleep. Deploy: Damage up to 5 Enemies on the opposite row by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/S0LjXhL.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Old Speartip: Asleep</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Ogroid, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

If at the start of your turn there are 3 or more Units on the opposite row, wake up. Deploy: Boost Units adjacent to this Unit by 1.
Old Speartip: Awake - 10 Strength, Agile, Ogroid, Loyal, Gold. If at the start of your turn there are 2 or fewer Units on the opposite row, fall asleep. Deploy: Damage up to 5 Enemies on the opposite row by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/Ym3p3Mb.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Abaya</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Siege, Necrophage, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Spawn Torrential Rain, Clear Skies or Lacerate.
Bug Fix: Water Hag will not activate abilities triggered on Consume.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/pUskMzg.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Brewess</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Siege, Mage, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Play all Crone units from your deck.
Added Mage Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/3FvSxKQ.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Frightener: Dormant</name>
            <text>10 Strength, Agile, Construct, Disloyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Move a Unit on another row on this side to this row. Draw the top card from your Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/s1aDeef.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Colossal Ifrit</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Siege, Construct, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Spawn 3 Lesser Fire Elementals.
Lesser Fire Elemental: 1 Strength, Melee, Doomed, Construct. Deploy: Damage a random Enemy by 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/5sSRCch.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Imperial Manticore</name>
            <text>9 Strength, Siege, Beast, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy, Brave: Strengthen self by 4.
Added Beast Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/6MuN1JX.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Jotunn</name>
            <text>Jotunn, Monsters, Ogroid, 6 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Move 3 adjacent Enemies to this Unit’s row on their side and Damage them by 2.
Lord of Undvik still exists as Hjalmar's Token and was given Ice Giant Artwork from The Witcher 3 Gwent. Old Lord of Undvik Artwork was given to new Monsters standalone card - Jotunn. Added Ogroid Tag to Jotunn and Lord of Undvik.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/XRWUEAG.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Maerolorn</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Agile, Necrophage, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Trigger the Deathwish of 3 Units to the right.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/BsiXKyb.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Monster Nest</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Silver, Epic.

Spawn a Bronze Necrophage or Insectoid Unit and Boost it by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/GOpr4lK.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Mourntart</name>
            <text>2 Strength, Agile, Necrophage, 1-Turn Timer, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

After 1 turn, at the start of your turn, Consume all Units in your Graveyard, but only Boost self by 1 for each.
Removed Devourer Tag. Added Necrophage Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/jgVWSGi.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Nithral</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Agile, Wild Hunt, Silver, Epic.

Frost Damage on your opponent’s side is increased to 3.
Removed Armor.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/Mfg8dS8.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Toad Prince</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Siege, Cursed, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Discard a non-Gold unit and absorb its strength, then draw a card.
Removed Devourer Tag. Added Cursed Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/ewiPmPr.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Weavess</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Siege, Mage, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Play all Crone units from your deck.
Added Mage Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/J4JrvoU.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Whispess</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Siege, Mage, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Play all Crone units from your deck.
Added Mage Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/XcEfTqR.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ancient Foglet</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Agile, Necrophage, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Every turn, at the start of your turn, Boost self by 1 if Fog is anywhere on the Board.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/OvuMSzb.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Arachas Behemoth</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Siege, Insectoid, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Whenever an Ally Consumes a card, Spawn an Arachas and Damage self by 1 (ignoring Armor). Deploy: Gain 2 Armor.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/hxd6tOz.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Arachas Drone</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Ranged, Insectoid, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Play all Arachasae from your Deck.
Added Insectoid Tag. Removed Breedable Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/guyrHR4.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Archgriffin</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Agile, Beast, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Clear Weather from the row on your side.
Added Beast Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/IMlv5yH.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Celaeno Harpy</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Agile, Beast, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Spawn 2 Harpy Eggs to the left of this Unit.
Harpy Egg: 1 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Loyal, Bronze. When Consumed by another Unit, Boost that Unit by an additional 5. Deathwish: Spawn a Harpy on a random row.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/6woYdi5.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Chort</name>
            <text>Monsters (standalone), 6 Strength,  Relict, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy, Brave: Strengthen self by 4 Added as a standalone Monsters card. Prize-Winning Cow's Chort token still exists and was given an ability.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/sMDlpzk.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Primordial D'ao</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Melee, Construct, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Give this Unit a Shield. Deathwish: Spawn 2 Lesser Earth Elementals at the end of the row
Lesser Earth Elemental: 2 Strength, Melee, Doomed, Construct, Loyal, Bronze.
Added Construct Tag to Earth Elemental and Lesser Earth Elemental. Replaced Lesser Earth Elemental's Fleeting Tag with Doomed.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/7Q93fHk.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Drowner</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Necrophage, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Move a Unit to this row on its side.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/RBiYPj3.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ekimmara</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Agile, Vampire, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Gain Resilience. Deploy: Consume an Ally.
Devourer Tag removed.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/CPNcdON.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Fiend</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Melee, Relict, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Toggle a Unit’s Lock. If it’s an Enemy, Damage it by half its Power (rounding down and ignoring Armor).
Added Relict Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/kJjfiv1.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Foglet</name>
            <text>2 Strength, Agile, Necrophage, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Whenever you apply Fog to an opposing row, play this Unit from your Deck or Resurrect it on that row on your side. When all Fog has been cleared from the Board, Destroy this Unit.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/2NokGDo.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ghoul</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Melee, Necrophage, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Consume a random unit from either Graveyard.
Removed Devourer Tag. Added Necrophage Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/S7mMUnl.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Harpy</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Agile, Beast, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Trigger the Deathwish of Units adjacent to this Unit.
Removed Harpy Tag. Added Beast Tag. Harpy Egg Token was removed from Harpy and attached to Celaeno Harpy.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/wrUEET0.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Harpy Egg</name>
            <text>1 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Loyal, Bronze. 

When Consumed by another Unit, Boost that Unit by an additional 5. Deathwish: Spawn a Harpy on a random row.
Note: Now spawned by Celaeno Harpy instead of a Harpy.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/CKIKscj.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ice Giant</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Ogroid, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

If Frost is anywhere on the Board, Boost self by 5. When the last Frost is cleared, Damage self by 5.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/2o0m2tW.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Nekker</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Melee, Ogroid, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Whenever an Ally Consumes a card while this Unit is in your Hand, Deck or on your side of the Board, Boost self by 1. Deathwish: Play a Nekker from your Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/9bmLltK.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Nekker Warrior</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Melee, Ogroid, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Choose a Bronze Ally and create 2 base copies of it on the bottom of your Deck.
Added Ogroid Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/M20Oo2l.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Predatory Dive</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Siege, Beast, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Move a card from one Graveyard to the other.
Removed Brave Ability.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/agbO508.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Vran Warrior</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Draconid, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Consume the Unit to the right. Every 2 turns, at the start of your turn, Consume the Unit to the right.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/2fGvvwO.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Wild Hunt Hound</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Melee, Wild Hunt, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Play a Biting Frost card from your Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/m22LCIZ.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Wild Hunt Navigator</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Siege, Wild Hunt, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Choose a different Bronze Wild Hunt Ally. Play a copy of it from your Deck.
.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/SmP5FCt.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Wild Hunt Rider</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Wild Hunt, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

At the end of the Round, keep this Unit on the Board if you lost. If this Unit is part of a Trio at the end of your turn, Boost it by 1.
Weather was reworked. Weather Immunity was removed.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/hCWBwVc.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Wild Hunt Warrior</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Melee, Wild Hunt, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Damage an Enemy by 3. If it was Destroyed, Boost self by 2.
Weather was reworked. Weather Immunity was removed.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/vf9g9FN.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Wyvern</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Siege, Draconid, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Damage an Enemy by 3.
Removed Brave ability.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/nHueep9.jpg">MO</set>
        </card>

<!-- [ST] ScoiaTael -->


        <card>
            <name>Brouver Hoog</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Stubborn, Dwarf, Loyal, Leader, Legendary.

Spawn Brouver Hoog. Deploy: Play a Silver Unit from your Deck. Shuffle the others back.
General change: Added Doomed and Stubborn Tags to all Leaders due to their new ability of Spawning themselves.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/E3Ui0Fr.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Eithné</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Stubborn, Dryad, Loyal, Leader, Legendary.

Spawn Eithné. Deploy: Resurrect a Special card..
General change: Added Doomed and Stubborn Tags to all Leaders due to their new ability of Spawning themselves.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/Cq4LaIi.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Francesca Findabair</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Stubborn, Elf, Loyal, Leader, Legendary.

Spawn: Francesca. Deploy: Mulligan up to 3 cards.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/kRMs2QV.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Aglaïs</name>
            <text>10 Strength, Agile, Dryad, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: You may Resurrect a Special card from your opponent's Graveyard. If you do, Weaken self by 4.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/sKK2xUP.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Iorveth</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Elf, Loyal, Gold, Legendary. 

Whenever an Enemy moves to a different row, Damage it by 2. Deploy: Damage an Enemy by 4.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/wZMunVH.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Isengrim Faoiltiarna</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Agile, Elf, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Play a Bronze or Silver Ambush card from your Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/5IuIOa1.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ithlinne Aegli</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Elf, Mage, Disloyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Play a Bronze Special card from your Deck, then Spawn a copy of it. Shuffle the others back.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/Y5gBi9f.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Milva</name>
            <text>9 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: If neither player has passed, return the Highest Enemy to your opponent's Hand, then return the Highest Ally to your Hand.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/ffgxwyU.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Saesenthessis</name>
            <text>9 Strength, Agile, Draconid, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Boost self by 1 for each Dwarf Ally (including Golds). Damage an Enemy by the number of Elf Allies (including Golds).</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/WHgwk2U.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Saskia</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Agile, Draconid, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Orders: Play this Unit from your Deck on a random row.
Saskia's Human Form was re.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/cyqD1OX.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Schirrú</name>
            <text>10 Strength, Agile, Elf, Loyal, Gold, Legendary. 

Deploy: You may Transform a card from your Hand (can be Gold) into Scorch.
Removed Ambush effect and Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/9oS0eqT.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Zoltan Chivay</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Dwarf, Loyal, Gold, Legendary. 

Deploy: Move 3 Units to this row on their side. If they are Allies, Strengthen them by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/pFrTKNg.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Aelirenn</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Ranged, Elf, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Play from deck when 5 or more Elves are on your side.
Removed +1 buff to all Elves, when Aelirenn is played.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/NRHCBsU.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Barclay Els</name>
            <text>2 Strength, Siege, Dwarf, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Play a random Bronze or Silver Dwarf from your Deck and Boost it by 3.
The Gold Dwarves won't be taken into consideration anymore.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/Uvo726R.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Braenn</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Ranged, Dryad, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Remove an amount equal to this unit's strength from an opposing non-Gold unit.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/TlsqjFO.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ciaran aep Easnillen</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Elf, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Toggle a Unit's Lock and move it to this row on its side.
Removed Ambush effect and Tag</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/Gov3amr.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dennis Cranmer</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Melee, Dwarf, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Strengthen all other Bronze and Silver Dwarves in your Deck, Hand and on your side of the Board by 1.
Now Loyal-only.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/QyFLgHI.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ele'yas</name>
            <text>9 Strength, Melee, Elf, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Destroy an Ally and Damage an Enemy by the Destroyed Ally's Power.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/pjXfF2S.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ida Emean aep Sivney</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Siege, Elf, Mage, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Spawn Impenetrable Fog, Clear Skies or Quen Sign.
Removed Ambush effect and Tag. Now Loyal-only.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/FgInbl3.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Malena</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Elf, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Every turn, at the start of your turn, move a random Unit on another row on this side to this row. Deploy: Gain 3 Armor.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/diAsQil.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Morenn</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Ambush, Dryad, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Ambush: When an Enemy appears, turn this Unit over and Damage that Enemy by 5.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/SruecEz.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Nature's Gift</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Silver, Epic.

Play a Bronze or Silver Special card from your Deck. Shuffle the others back.
Removed Fleeting Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/HTj0dph.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Sheldon Skaggs</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Dwarf, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Move all Units on the row to random rows on the same side and Boost self by 1 for each.
Bug Fix: Sheldon Skaggs' ability fixed to reflect his tooltip (he Boosts instead of Strengthening).</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/J8zke44.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Toruviel</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Ambush, Elf, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Ambush: When your opponent passes, turn this Unit over and Boost 2 Units on each side by 2.
Now Loyal-only.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/GmYYIII.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Yaevinn</name>
            <text>12 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Elf, Disloyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Draw the top Unit and top Special card from your Deck. Keep 1 and shuffle the other back.
Weather was reworked. Weather Immunity was Removed.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/x09ehpc.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Yarpen Zigrin</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Siege, Dwarf, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Whenever a Dwarf Ally (including Golds) is played, Boost self by 1. Deploy: Gain Resilience</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/bIvrw84.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Blue Mountain Elite</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Agile, Elf, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Whenever this Unit is moved, Boost it by 2. Deploy: Play all Blue Mountain Commandos from your Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/UJEYCYL.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dol Blathanna Archer</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Ranged, Elf, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Damage Enemies by 3 and then 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/wUXM1hi.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dol Blathanna Bomber</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Ranged, Elf, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Spawn a Fireball Trap on an opposing row.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/FpsavCT.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dol Blathanna Bowman</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Ranged, Elf, Loyal, Bronze, Common. 

Every time this Unit is moved, Damage a random Enemy by 2. Deploy: Damage a Unit by 2. </text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/CjLPy86.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dol Blathanna Sentry</name>
            <text>2 Strength, Agile, Elf, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Whenever you play a Special card, Boost this Unit by 1 while in your Hand, Deck or on your side of the Board.
Dol Blathanna Protector will not be buffed by Gold cards played.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/lr0HDCc.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dwarven Mercenary</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Dwarf, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Move a Unit on another row to this row on its side. If it's an Ally, Boost it by 3.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/HjbxrN2.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dwarven Skirmisher</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Siege, Dwarf, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Damage an enemy by 3. If the Unit was not Destroyed, Boost self by 2.
Bug Fix: Fixed Dwarven Skirmisher's tooltip to match his ability.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/oToPfH0.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Elven Mercenary</name>
            <text>2 Strength, Agile, Elf, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Draw the top 2 Bronze Special cards in your Deck. Play 1 and shuffle the other back.
Removed "if this unit is spying..." effect.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/l9QgpGc.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Hawker Healer</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Elf, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Boost 2 Units to the right by 3.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/2feB7e0.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Hawker Smuggler</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Ranged, Elf, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Whenever a Unit appears on your opponent's side, Boost self by 1.
Added Elf Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/kERpKcp.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Hawker Support</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Siege, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Boost a Unit in your Hand by 3.
Removed Elf Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/jGJ1ALA.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Incinerating Trap</name>
            <text>1 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Disloyal, Bronze.

After 1 turn, at the end of your turn, damage all other Units on the Row by 2 strength and banish self.
Will not ignore armor anymore, Added Doomed Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/v422ZpJ.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Mahakam Defender</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Melee, Dwarf, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Gain Resilience.
General change: All Resilient Units will gain Resilence when placed - when the next round starts the Resilience is removed.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/0yyu6qG.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Mahakam Guard</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Melee, Dwarf, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Boost an Ally by 3. If it's a Dwarf, Boost by 4 instead.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/QArs2I7.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Vrihedd Brigade</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Elf, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Clear Weather from the row on your side and move a Unit to this row on its side.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/g0KXNd6.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Vrihedd Dragoon</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Siege, Elf, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Every turn, at the start of your turn, Boost a random Loyal Unit in your Hand by 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/mi4QM2R.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Vrihedd Neophyte</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Melee, Elf, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Whenever you Mulligan a card, Damage a random Enemy by 2.
Removed Armor from Commando Neophyte.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/rYLDQnt.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Vrihedd Officer</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Siege, Elf, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Mulligan a card.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/9rcfXZz.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Vrihedd Sappers</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Ambush, Elf, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Ambush: After 2 turns, at the start of your turn, turn this Unit over.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/NWf1FJF.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Vrihedd Vanguard</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Elf, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Whenever you Mulligan a card, Boost self by 1 while in your Hand, Deck or on your side of the Board.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/CYXMrXy.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Wardancer</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Melee, Elf, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Whenever you Mulligan this Unit, play it from your Deck immediately.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/jDZDriv.jpg">ST</set>
        </card>

<!-- [SK] Skellige -->


        <card>
            <name>Bran Tuirseach</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Stubborn, Loyal, Leader, Legendary.

Spawn King Bran. Deploy: Discard up to 3 cards from your Deck and Strengthen all Units among them by 1. Then shuffle your deck.
Bug Fix: Fixed an issue with King Bran's carousel displaying the wrong number of cards to discard.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/fArE2H6.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Crach an Craite</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Stubborn, Loyal, Leader, Legendary.

Spawn: Crach an Craite. Deploy: Play the Highest Loyal Bronze or Silver Unit in your Deck, Strengthen it by 3 and Damage it by 1.
No longer spawns Clan an Craite Warriors.
General change: Added Doomed and Stubborn Tags to all Leaders due to their new ability of Spawning themselves.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/3Q2RWa1.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Harald the Cripple</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Stubborn, Loyal, Leader, Legendary.

Spawn Harald the Cripple. Deploy: Damage a Unit by 5. If this Destroys it, repeat this ability with Damage Power reduced by 1.
General change: Added Doomed and Stubborn Tags to all Leaders due to their new ability of Spawning themselves.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/k1RgUlj.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Birna Bran</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Disloyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Move a Unit from your opponent's Graveyard to yours. Every turn, at the start of your turn, Damage self by 1 and Units adjacent to this Unit by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/FMw686o.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Cerys an Craite</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

After 4 Units are Resurrected on your side while this Unit is in the Graveyard, Resurrect it.
No longer Queensguard connected only.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/qwFYp2K.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Coral</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Mage, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Pick a Unit and Damage all Units on its row by half their Power (rounding down and ignoring Armor).</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/cRr1YYD.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ermion</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Draw the top 2 cards from your Deck, then Discard 2 cards (can be Golds) from your Hand.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/IY1P81M.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Hjalmar an Craite</name>
            <text>13 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Spawn Lord of Undvik on the leftmost side of the opposite row.
Lord of Undvik - 5 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Ogroid, Disloyal, Silver. When removed from the battlefield, add 10 strength to any Hjalmars on the opposite side.
Added  Doomed Tag to Lord of Undvik. The ability to Boost Hjalmar was again moved to Lord of Undvik.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/ys5dKsv.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Kambi</name>
            <text>1 Strength, Agile, Doomed, 3-Turn Timer, Disloyal, Gold, Legendary.

After 3 turns, at the start of your turn, Spawn Hemdall.
Hemdall: 16 Strength, Melee, Doomed, Disloyal, Gold. Deploy: Destroy all Units on the Board. Clear all Weather. Banish all Allied Kambis.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/VMDOICD.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Madman Lugos</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Discard a Bronze Unit from your Deck and Damage a Unit by the Discarded Unit's base Power.
No longer Timer-based ability.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/2315XXl.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Vabjorn</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Cursed, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Every turn, at the end of your turn, Damage by 2 every Damaged Enemy with 2 Power or less.
.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/GS990jp.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Wild Boar of the Sea</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Machine, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Every turn, at the start of your turn, Strengthen the Unit to the left by 1 and Damage the Unit to the right by 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/ILl25aX.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Blueboy Lugos</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Melee, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Veteran 1. Deploy: Spawn a Spectral Whale on your opponent's side.
Spectral Whale: 3 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Specter, Disloyal, Silver. Every turn, at the start of your turn move this unit to a random row on its side and Damage all other Units on the Row by 1.
Added Specter Tag to Spectral Whale. Replaced Spectral Whale's Fleeting Tag with Doomed. Weather was reworked. Weather Immunity was removed.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/NGYgkNc.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Champion of Hov</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Ogroid, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Every turn, at the start of your turn, Strengthen this Unit by 2 if it is the only Unit on the row.
Added Ogroid Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/HoOhNhO.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Djenge Frett</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Veteran 1. Deploy: Damage 3 Allies by 1 and Strengthen self by 1 for each.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/RXmGmxQ.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Donar an Hindar</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Ranged, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Veteran: 1. Deploy: Toggle a Unit's Lock. Discard a random Bronze card from your opponent's Deck to your Graveyard.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/qiFJDIT.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Draig Bon-Dhu</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Siege, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Strengthen up to 2 Units in your Graveyard by 3.
Note: Draig Bon-Dhu's ability is now optional.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/hhY4IZA.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Gremist</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Siege, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Spawn Impenetrable Fog, Clear Skies or Bloodcurdling Roar.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/b7DSD7h.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Holger Blackhand</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Siege, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Veteran 1. Deploy: Damage a Unit by 5. If it was Destroyed, Strengthen 1 of the Highest Units in your Graveyard by 3.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/JbDIO2c.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Jutta an Dimun</name>
            <text>12 Strength, Melee, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Veteran 1. Deploy: Damage self by 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/rEnuetB.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Morkvarg</name>
            <text>9 Strength, Melee, Cursed, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Whenever this Unit is Discarded or Destroyed, Resurrect it and Weaken it by half its Power (rounding up).</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/sNbvXRw.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Restore</name>
            <text>Event, Special, Silver, Epic.

Return a Unit from your Graveyard to your Hand, then Discard a card from your Hand.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/RKHjaNC.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Sigrdrifa</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Siege, Doomed, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Resurrect a Unit.
Note: No longer boosts self whenever a card is resurrected.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/wrEZx9d.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Skjall</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Siege, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Veteran 1. After 2 turns, at the end of your turn, convert this Unit's current Power into base Power.
Craven Revived Token was transformed into Necromancy Neutral Special.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/3u6rIBN.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Svanrige Tuirseach</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Siege, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Veteran: Strengthen self by 1. Deploy: Draw a card (including Golds) then Discard a card from your Hand.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/4NXXXA0.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Udalryk</name>
            <text>12 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Cursed, Disloyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Draw the top 2 cards from your Deck. Keep one and Discard the other.
Note: Udalryk's ability is no longer optional. Clarified the tooltip.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/3wWA6M4.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>An Craite Armorsmith</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Veteran: Strengthen self by 1. Deploy: Heal 3 Units to the left.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/Lzwy0oN.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>An Craite Blacksmith</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Siege, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Veteran: Strengthen self by 1. Deploy: Strengthen a Unit by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/aSlavuT.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>An Craite Longship</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Siege, Machine, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Whenever you Discard a Unit, Damage a random Enemy by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/8BaCD72.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>An Craite Raider</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Melee, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Veteran: 1. Whenever this Unit is Discarded, Resurrect it immediately.
Note: Consuming Clan An Craite Raiders will not count as discarding them.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/SfWpaEM.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>An Craite Warcrier</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Veteran: 1. Deploy: Boost 3 Damaged Units to the left by half their Power (rounding up).
Note: Removed Effort ability.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/RucItKJ.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>An Craite Warrior</name>
            <text>9 Strength, Melee, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Veteran: 1. Deploy: Damage self by 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/9YlEaRV.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Brokvar Hunter</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Regressing, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Whenever a Unit adjacent to this Unit is Damaged, Strengthen self by 1. Deploy: Damage a Unit by 3.
Removed Veteran Ability.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/7aDGDkd.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dimun Light Longship</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Regressing, Machine, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Every turn, at the start of your turn, Damage the Unit to the right by 1, then Strengthen self by 2.
Weather was reworked. Weather Immunity was removed.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/9TAoJzr.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dimun Pirate</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Veteran: Strengthen self by 1. Deploy: Discard all copies of this Unit from your Deck.
Weather was reworked. Weather Immunity was removed.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/TJohAam.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Dimun Pirate Captain</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Veteran: 1. Whenever you Discard a Unit, Boost self by 1 while in your Hand, Deck or on your side of the Board.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/InYK670.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Drummond Queensguard</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Melee, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Resurrect all your Queensguards.
Removed Veteran ability.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/MSB7e1g.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Drummond Shieldmaid</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Ranged, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Damage a Unit by 2. If it was already Damaged, play a Clan Drummond Shieldmaiden from your Deck.
Removed Veteran ability.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/dflzhZs.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Heymaey Skald</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Veteran: Strengthen self by 1. Deploy: Boost 3 Units to the left by 3, 2 and 1 respectively.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/uBeG5he.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Priestess of Freya</name>
            <text>1 Strength, Siege, Doomed, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Resurrect a Bronze Unit from your Graveyard.
Note: Can be resurrected if discarded. Replaced Permadeath with Doomed tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/p7yEbiK.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Savage Bear</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Melee, Cursed, Beast, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

After an Enemy is played from any Hand and its Deploy ability resolves, Damage it by 1.
Note: Savage Bear will no longer affect spawned units anymore.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/HF9ROUK.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Svalblod Butcher</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Melee, Regressing, Cursed, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Strengthen self by 1 for each Damaged Ally (including Golds), then Damage self by 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/ScSChDL.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Svalblod Ravager</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Cursed, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Retaliation: Transform into a Raging Bear.
Raging Bear: 10 Strength, Melee, Cursed, Beast, Loyal, Bronze. No Ability.
Removed Shapeshifter tag. Added Cursed tag. Removed Bear tag. Added Beast tag to Raging Bear. Weather was reworked. Weather Immunity was removed.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/fR4BYVl.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Tuirseach Archer</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Siege, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Veteran: 1. Deploy: Damage 3 Units by 1.
Bug Fix: Fixed an issue with milling Clan Brokvar Archer x4.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/WWETFIZ.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Tuirseach Axeman</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Gain 2 Armor. Whenever an Enemy is Damaged, Boost self by 1.
Removed Veteran ability.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/4GFWeui.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Tuirseach Skirmisher</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Melee, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Veteran: Strengthen self by 1. Whenever this Unit enters the Graveyard, Strengthen it by 3.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/moyPtWe.jpg">SK</set>
        </card>


<!-- [NG] Nilfgaard -->


        <card>
            <name>Emhyr var Emreis</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Doomed, Stubborn, Agile, Leader, Legendary.

Spawn Emhyr var Emreis. Deploy: Return an Ally to your Hand, then play a card from your Hand (can be Gold).</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/epjimjo.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Jan Calveit</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Stubborn, Leader, Legendary.

Spawn John Calveit. Deploy: Look at the top 3 Bronze or Silver cards in your Deck. Play 1. The others remain on top.
Priority change: Imperial Golems will now be played from your Deck before John Calveit's ability triggers.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/aULvqt1.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Morvran Voorhis</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Stubborn, Leader, Legendary.

Spawn Morvran Voorhis. Deploy: Reveal up to 3 cards from either player's Hand (can be Golds).
General change: Added Doomed and Stubborn Tags to all Leaders due to their new ability of Spawning themselves.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/5Em6gCS.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Treason</name>
            <text>Event, Gold, Special, Legendary.

Lock and Destroy an Enemy.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/DjoU1b2.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Cahir Dyffryn</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Stubborn, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: If playing as Nilfgaard, trigger your Leader's Deploy ability.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/lc2RMrk.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Letho of Gulet</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Agile, Witcher, Loyal / Disloyal, Gold, Legendary.

>Deploy: If Spying, set own base Power to 1. Deploy: Banish 2 Units to each side of this Unit and Boost this Unit by their Power.
Bug Fix: Fixed the issue whereby Disloyal Agile Units (e.g. Letho of Gulet) couldn't be played on rows other than Melee.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/gRhQfRE.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Leo Bonhart</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Reveal a Unit in your Hand (can be Gold) and Damage an Enemy by its Base Power.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/qMhPPGX.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Menno Coehoorn</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Destroy all Spying Enemies.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/TLjMvwi.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Rainfarn of Attre</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Play a Disloyal Unit from your Deck. Shuffle the others back.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/F4cQrWR.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Stefan Skellen</name>
            <text>10 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Choose any card from your Deck and place it on top. Then shuffle the rest of your Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/OHqX1dq.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Tibor Eggebracht</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: If neither player has passed, Boost self by 15, then your opponent draws the top Bronze card from their Deck and Reveals it.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/gY4SETb.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Vattier de Rideaux</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Reveal up to 2 cards from your Hand (can be Golds). For each, Reveal 1 random card from your opponent's Hand (can be Gold).
Tooltip clarification: The tooltip now properly states, that Vattier's effect works on Gold card.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/qpwIrZc.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Vilgefortz</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Agile, Mage, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Destroy an Ally, then play a top card from your Deck (including Golds) or Clash: Destroy an Enemy, then your opponent draws a revealed Bronze card.
Priority change: Priority change; Roach won't come out until Vilgefortz ability is triggered.}
Note: Not sure if true, but Vilgefortz had always drawn a Bronze for the opponent if you chose to destroy a unit on their side, the tooltip didn't state so until now (?)</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/FMabYXI.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Xarthisius</name>
            <text>10 Strength, Agile, Mage, Loyal, Gold, Legendary.

Deploy: Look at the top 3 cards in your opponent's Deck. You may move 1 to the bottom of their Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/OJKJwnA.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Albrich</name>
            <text>9 Strength, Siege, Mage, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: If neither player has passed, each player draws the top card from their Deck. Your opponent's card is Revealed.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/rdLvBWj.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Assire var Anahid</name>
            <text>10 Strength, Siege, Mage, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Shuffle up to 2 cards from either Graveyard into that player's Deck.
Bug Fix: Fixed improper descriptions of Assire var Anahid's and Nenneke's carousels.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/aDRjJrT.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Auckes</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Ranged, Witcher, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Toggle 2 Units' Lock. If Enemies, Damage them by 1 as well.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/SlqzyL6.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Cantarella</name>
            <text>10 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Disloyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Draw the top card from your Deck. Keep it, or place it at the bottom of your Deck and draw the new top card.
Weather was reworked. Weather Immunity was Removed. Won't lose strength if not Spying (Reworked Treason and John Calveit. Added Doomed Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/xqbB0bN.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ceallach Dyffryn</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Melee, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Move 2 Bronze Spying Enemies to your side.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/nHSndlh.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Cynthia</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Ranged, Mage, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Reveal 1 of the Highest Units in your opponent's Hand (including Golds) and Boost self by its Power.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/3DehPDa.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>False Ciri</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Loyal / Disloyal, Silver, Epic.

If this Unit is Spying at the start of your turn, Boost it by 1. If it is Spying when your opponent passes, move it to the opposite side. Deploy: When you play this Unit on your side, Strengthen it by 3.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/zjFv9NK.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Fringilla Vigo</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Agile, Mage, Loyal / Disloyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: If Spying, set own base Power to 1. Deploy: Set the Power of the Unit on the right to that of the Unit on the left.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/MZR43NF.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Joachim de Wett</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Disloyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Play the top Loyal Bronze or Silver Unit in your Deck and Boost it by 10.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/GhMifnu.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Peter Saar Gwynleve</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Melee, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Reset a Unit. If it's an Ally, Strengthen it by 3. If it's an Enemy, Weaken it by 3.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/h2jDpkH.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Serrit</name>
            <text>9 Strength, Melee, Witcher, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Set the Power of a Revealed Unit in your opponent's Hand to 1.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/7MYhYNx.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Sweers</name>
            <text>7 Strength, Melee, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Choose an Enemy or a Revealed opposing Unit and move all copies of it from your opponent's Deck to their Graveyard.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/DDurkAm.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>The Guardian</name>
            <text>10 Strength, Melee, Construct, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deathwish: Create 2 Lesser Guardians (6 strength, no ability) on the top of your opponent's Deck.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/ZCTEbof.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Treason</name>
            <text>Event, Silver, Special, Silver, Epic.

Play the bottom card from your opponent's Deck..</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/DjoU1b2.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Vanhemar</name>
            <text>3 Strength, Siege, Mage, Loyal, Silver, Epic.

Deploy: Spawn Biting Frost, Clear Skies or Stammelford's Tremors.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/9sgw1CH.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Alba Pikeman</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

After 2 turns, at the start of your turn, play an Alba Pikeman on the row.Deploy: Gain 2 Armor.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/01i0PoP.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Alba Spearman</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Ranged, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Give this Unit a Shield.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/7KKzO41.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Alchemist</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Ranged, Mage, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Reveal a card.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/8RoAqJy.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Ambassador</name>
            <text>2 Strength, Agile, Disloyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Boost an Ally by 10.
Bug Fix: Fixed an issue whereby Ambassador would Boost Units by 12 instead of 10 when activated by Vicovaro Novice.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/SQggrSQ.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Combat Engineer</name>
            <text>2 Strength, Siege, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Toggle a Unit's Resilience.
Note: Now able to toggle both players' units.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/3bl0L1m.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Daerlan Soldier</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Melee, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

When this Unit is Revealed, play it and draw the top card from your Deck.
Bug Fix: Fixed an issue whereby Daerlan Foot Soldiers wouldn't draw a card if they were killed with Morenn or Savage Bear.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/xUQKtxg.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Deithwen Arbalest</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Ranged, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Damage an Enemy by 3. If it was Boosted, Damage it by 5 instead.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/a969qD4.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Emissary</name>
            <text>2 Strength, Agile, Disloyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Draw the top 2 Bronze Units (not including Emissaries) from your Deck. Play 1 and shuffle the other back.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/plDmb8t.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Experimental Remedy</name>
            <text>1 Strength, Ranged, Doomed, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Resurrect a Bronze Unit from your opponent's Graveyard.
Added Doomed Tag.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/EotoFDf.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Fire Scorpion</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Siege, Machine, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Whenever this Unit is Revealed, Damage a random Enemy by 3. Deploy: Damage an Enemy by 3.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/q0PXRmN.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Impera Brigade</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Melee, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Whenever you play a Spying Unit (including Golds), Boost self by 2. Deploy: Boost self by 2 for each Spying Enemy (including Golds).
Note: Now the tooltip correctly mentions Gold cards.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/CnpjH4z.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Impera Enforcers</name>
            <text>8 Strength, Ranged, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Look at the top card in your Deck. If it's Bronze, gain 2 Armor. If it's Silver, Boost self by 1. If it's Gold, Promote self.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/GiCVU4b.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Imperial Golem</name>
            <text>2 Strength, Construct, Melee, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Orders: Summon this Unit.
Priority change: Imperial Golems will now be played from your Deck before John Calveit's ability triggers.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/PVAa0sN.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Mangonel</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Machine, Siege, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Whenever a card is Revealed, Damage a random Enemy by 2.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/zPrfbKI.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Nauzicaa Brigade</name>
            <text>5 Strength, Ranged, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Damage a Spying Unit by 5. If it was Destroyed, Strengthen self by 4.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/vTxErfV.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Nauzicaa Sergeant</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Clear Weather from the row on your side and Boost 1 Ally or Revealed Unit in your Hand by 3</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/QJo4iFc.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Nilfgaardian Knight</name>
            <text>10 Strength, Melee, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Gain 2 Armor. Deploy: Reveal a random card from your Hand (can be Gold).
Always revealed all cards (incl. Golds), now the tooltip states it so.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/qS21t48.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Rot Tosser</name>
            <text>6 Strength, Siege, Machine, Loyal, Bronze, Common.

Deploy: Spawn a Cow Carcass on your opponent's row.
Cow Carcass: 1 Strength, Agile, Doomed, Beast, Disloyal, Bronze. Timer 2, Turn End: Destroy the Weakest Unit(s) on the row, then Banish this Unit.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/0mLKtAF.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Spotter</name>
            <text>4 Strength, Agile, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Whenever either player Reveals a card, Boost self by 1 while in your Hand, Deck or on your side of the Board.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/ZtJIlws.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>

        <card>
            <name>Vicovaro Novice</name>
            <text>1 Strength, Mage, Siege, Loyal, Bronze, Rare.

Deploy: Trigger the ability of a Spying Enemy Ambassador or Emissary.
Bug Fix: Fixed an issue whereby Ambassador would Boost Units by 12 instead of 10 when activated by Vicovaro Novice.</text>
            <set picURL="https://i.imgur.com/CayDWpK.jpg">NG</set>
        </card>


        
    </cards>
</cockatrice_carddatabase>
